ihopkc.org 2019-11-12

# Privacy Policy - International House of Prayer

IHOPKC recognizes your right to confidentiality and is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. You can expect to be notified of:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected
  * How is the information used
  * What kinds of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under the company’s control
  * How you can correct inaccuracies in your information

_We do not share or distribute information to any third party or other organization._

For any questions regarding these statements, please contact us.

### Your personal information

We do not collect personal information when you visit our site unless you signup for a service, place an order, register or contact us through our contact page.

When you signup for a service, we will ask you for personal information All information is transmitted via a secure encrypted server using 256 Bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, the approved industry standard (see Security section below). We may use your personal information to contact you for account purposes.

When you submit feedback or questions via e-mail, or contact us for information about our website, we will request your name, e-mail address, & phone number. We use this information solely to respond to your inquiries and to verify your identity.

_We do not share any general demographic information with advertisers and partners even as aggregated information that cannot be used in any way to identify you._

_IHOPKC.org certifies that all personal information relating to its members and clients, including email addresses and all other personal information, will be kept confidential. We will never sell, lease, distribute, or otherwise disclose personal information to any other party._

### Security

We use industry-standard SSL authentication to guarantee the confidentiality and privacy of online transactions through our site. SSL authentication and 256-bit encryption (scrambling) ensure that your online transaction and account information are safe from third-party interception.

### Cookies

_We do not use “cookies”_. Although cookies reduce the time required to login, we opted not to use it for security purposes.

### Updates

[IHOPKC.org](https://www.ihopkc.org/) provides you with the opportunity to update or change any information you previously provided.

### Your consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of these information as outlined here. If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page so you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances do we disclose it.

### Donation Information

We do not store any credit card information associated with donations on our servers. All information is encrypted and sent to [Authorize.net](http://www.authorize.net/) where they securely store all information.
